Guide to the John Anthony Danaher Papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- U.S. SENATE CORRESPONDENCE FILES, 1936-1945; Series I; 15.75 linear feet (39 boxes)
  - Personal
    - 78th Congress
      - Statements and opinons, 1940-1944 (Box 17, Folder 266)
  - General
    - 78th Congress
      - Roosevelt, Mrs. Franklin D., 1940-1944 (Box 17, Folder 267)
      - Ryan, Francis, 1943 (Box 17, Folder 268)
      - Schatz, Nathan, 1943-1944 (Box 17, Folder 269)
      - Senate Republicans, 1944 (Box 17, Folder 270)
      - Sherman, Maurice, 1940-1941 (Box 17, Folder 271)
      - Silver, 1944 (Box 17, Folder 272)
      - Smith, George, 1941-1944 (Box 17, Folder 273)
      - Tilton, Eleanor Taft, 1943-1944 (Box 17, Folder 274-275a)
      - Uphaus, Willard, 1944 (Box 17, Folder 275b)
      - Villard, Oswald G., 1942 (Box 17, Folder 276)
      - War, conduct of, 1943-1944 (Box 17, Folder 277)
      - Wright, Herbert, 1944 (Box 17, Folder 278)
  - Legislation
    - 76th Congress
      - Aid to Allies: Committee to Defend America, 1940 (Box 18, Folder 279)
      - Aid to Britain, 1939-1940 (Box 18, Folder 280-282)
      - Excess profits tax, 1939-1941 (Box 18, Folder 283)
      - Foreign policy, 1938-1941 (Box 18, Folder 284)
      - National Guard, 1940 (Box 18, Folder 285)
      - Neutrality legislation
        - General, 1938-1939 (Box 18, Folder 286-288)
        - General, 1939-1940 (Box 19, Folder 289-290)
        - A - B, 1939 (Box 19, Folder 291)
        - Against, 1939 (Box 19, Folder 292)
        - C - D, 1939 (Box 19, Folder 293)
        - Changes or repeals, 1941 (Box 19, Folder 294)
        - E - G, 1939 (Box 19, Folder 295)
        - Embargo on horses and mules, 1939 (Box 19, Folder 296)
        - Export trade statistics, 1939 (Box 19, Folder 297)
        - For, 1939 (Box 19, Folder 298)
        - H - K, 1939 (Box 20, Folder 299)
        - L - M, 1939 (Box 20, Folder 300)
        - Law, 1941 (Box 20, Folder 301)
        - Letters to clergy, groups, 1939 (Box 20, Folder 302)
        - Modification of Neutrality Act of 1939 (Box 20, Folder 303)
        - N - S, 1939 (Box 20, Folder 304)
        - National Constitution Day Committee, 1940 (Box 20, Folder 305)
        - T - Z, 1939 (Box 20, Folder 306)
      - Silver, 1939-1940 (Box 20, Folder 307-308)
    - 77th Congress
      - Aid to Britain, 1940-1942 (Box 21, Folder 309-311)
      - Compulsory military training(conscription), 1940 (Box 21, Folder 312-314)
      - Convoys, 1941 (Box 21, Folder 315)
      - Defense aid for Lend-Lease bill, 1941 (Box 21, Folder 316)
      - Intervention, 1941 (Box 21, Folder 317)
      - Langer, William: (senator elect protest), 1940-1942 (Box 21, Folder 318)
      - Nominations, 1941-1942 (Box 21, Folder 319)
      - Non-Intervention, 1941 (Box 21, Folder 320)
      - 'Union Now', 1941-1942 (Box 21, Folder 321)
    - 78th Congress
      - Bills introducted by JAD, 1939-1944 (Box 21, Folder 322)
      - History of Bills and Resolutions, 1943 (Box 21, Folder 323)
      - "Last day in office", 1945 (Box 21, Folder 324)
      - Postwar foreign policy
        - General, 1943-1944 (Box 21, Folder 325-326)
        - Ball resolution, 1943 (Box 22, Folder 327)
        - Connally resolution, 1943-1944 (Box 22, Folder 328-330)
        - Fulbright resolution, 1943 (Box 22, Folder 331)
        - Library of Congress, 1943-1944 (Box 22, Folder 332)
      - Postwar internal communications, 1943 (Box 22, Folder 333)
      - Servicemen's vote (Green-Lucas bill), 1943-1944 (Box 22, Folder 334)
  - Committees
    - 76th Congress
      - Banking and Currency
        - Devaluation bill and stabilization, 1939 (Box 23, Folder 335)
        - Loans to Finland, 1940 (Box 23, Folder 336)
      - Judiciary
        - Criminal appeals, 1939-1940 (Box 23, Folder 337)
        - Habeus Corpus, 1939 (Box 23, Folder 338)
        - Licensing of corporations, 1940 (Box 23, Folder 339)
        - National defense, 1940 (Box 23, Folder 340)
        - Nye bills, 1939-1940 (Box 23, Folder 341-1942)
        - O'Mahoney Anti-Trust bill, 1939-1940 (Box 23, Folder 343)
        - Pocket-veto case, 1939-1940 (Box 23, Folder 344)
        - Subcommittee, 1939-1940 (Box 23, Folder 345)
        - Walter-Logan bill, 1939-1940 (Box 23, Folder 346)
        - Women, equal rights, 1934-1940 (Box 23, Folder 347)
      - Patents
        - Copyright, 1935-1940 (Box 24, Folder 348-349)
        - Court of patent appeals, 1936-1940 (Box 24, Folder 350-351)
    - 77th Congress
      - Finance
        - Administrative matters, 1941 (Box 24, Folder 352)
        - Excess profits tax, 1941 (Box 24, Folder 353-355)
        - Silverware tax, 1941 (Box 24, Folder 356)
        - Tax bill, 1942 (Box 24, Folder 357)
        - Tax bill, 1942 (Box 25, Folder 358-366)
      - Judiciary
        - Admiralty jurisdiction, extension, 1942 (Box 26, Folder 367)
        - Antitrust, 1942 (Box 26, Folder 368)
        - Biddle - Pound debate, 1941-1942 (Box 26, Folder 369)
        - Codification, 1942 (Box 26, Folder 370)
        - Committee rules, 1941-1942 (Box 26, Folder 371)
        - Federal Tort Claims bill, 1926-1942 (Box 26, Folder 372-374)
        - Indeterminate sentencing, 1941 (Box 26, Folder 375)
        - Judges, Trial of, 1941-1942 (Box 26, Folder 376)
        - Monopolies, 1941 (Box 26, Folder 377)
        - Obscene literature, 1941-1942 (Box 26, Folder 378)
        - Post offices and roads, [1941] (Box 27, Folder 379)
        - Propaganda agencies, 1941-1942 (Box 27, Folder 380)
        - War, Effective prosecution of, 1942 (Box 27, Folder 381)
        - War Powers Act, First, 1941-1943 (Box 27, Folder 382-383)
        - War Powers Act, Third, 1942 (Box 27, Folder 384)
        - Wiretapping, 1941 (Box 27, Folder 385)
      - Patents
        - National defense, 1942 (Box 27, Folder 386-387)
        - Patent proposals, 1939 (Box 27, Folder 388)
        - Trade-Mark registration, 1941-1942 (Box 27, Folder 389-390)
        - Miscellanea, 1931-1941 (Box 27, Folder 391-392)
    - 78th Congress
      - Banking and Currency
        - Board of Economic Warfare, 1940-1944 (Box 28, Folder 393-395)
        - Commodity Credit Act, 1943 (Box 28, Folder 396-397)
        - Cost of living stabilization, 1942 (Box 28, Folder 398)
        - Lending authority of the Reconstruction Finance Corporation, 1942 (Box 29, Folder 399)
        - Price control, 1942-1944 (Box 29, Folder 400)
        - Silver Purchase Act, 1942-1943 (Box 29, Folder 401)
      - Finance
        - Tax 1943, 1943-1944 (Box 29, Folder 402-406)
      - Judiciary
        - Admiralty jurisdiction, 1943 (Box 29, Folder 407)
        - Agriculture and forestry, 1944 (Box 29, Folder 408)
        - Bankruptcy Act, 1944 (Box 29, Folder 409)
        - Commerce protection, 1943-1944 (Box 29, Folder 410)
        - Convicts, escaped, 1943 (Box 29, Folder 411)
        - Counterfeiting, 1943 (Box 29, Folder 412)
        - Court attendants, 1944 (Box 29, Folder 413)
        - Court reporters, 1943 (Box 29, Folder 414)
        - Courts - U.S. party defendant, 1944 (Box 29, Folder 415)
        - Criminal code, 1943 (Box 29, Folder 416)
        - District Court of Alaska, 1943 (Box 29, Folder 417)
        - District Court of Connecticut, 1943 (Box 29, Folder 418)
        - Domicile for federal employees, 1944 (Box 29, Folder 419)
        - Enfranchisement, 1943 (Box 29, Folder 420)
        - Equal rights, 1936-1944 (Box 30, Folder 421-422)
        - Executive orders, validity, 1943 (Box 30, Folder 423)
        - Federal Corrections Act, 1943-1944 (Box 30, Folder 424)
        - Federal officers, Killing of, 1943 (Box 30, Folder 425)
        - Federal pay, Garnishment of, 1943-1944 (Box 30, Folder 426)
        - Fingerprinting, 1943 (Box 30, Folder 427)
        - Flag of the U.S., 1941-1943 (Box 30, Folder 428)
        - Foreign service courts, 1943-1944 (Box 30, Folder 429)
        - Fraudulent use of slugs, 1943-1944 (Box 30, Folder 430)
        - General, 1944 (Box 30, Folder 431)
        - Insurance business regulation
          - No. 1362, 1943 (Box 30, Folder 432-433)
          - No. 3270, 1943-1944 (Box 30, Folder 434)
          - No. 3270, 1944 (Box 31, Folder 435)
          - Joint hearing (Box 31, Folder 436)
          - Southeastern underwriters, 1943-1944 (Box 31, Folder 437-438)
        - Interstate larceny, 1943 (Box 31, Folder 439)
        - Judiciary code, 1943 (Box 31, Folder 440)
        - Jurors, selection of, 1943 (Box 31, Folder 441)
        - Juvenile delinquency, 1944 (Box 31, Folder 442)
        - Legislative program of attorney general, 1943 (Box 31, Folder 443)
        - Liquor shortage, 1943-1944 (Box 31, Folder 444-445)
        - Longshoremens' and Harbor Workers' Act, 1943 (Box 31, Folder 446)
        - McKeffar bill - executive appointments, 1943-1944 (Box 32, Folder 447)
        - Minor election, 1944 (Box 32, Folder 448)
        - Montgomery Ward Case, 1943-1944 (Box 32, Folder 449)
        - Municipal bankruptcies, 1944 (Box 32, Folder 450)
        - National Safety Council - incorporation, 1944 (Box 32, Folder 451)
        - Nominations
          - General, 1943-1944 (Box 32, Folder 452)
          - Allred, James, 1943 (Box 32, Folder 453)
          - Chandler, Stephen, 1943-1944 (Box 32, Folder 454)
          - Lawrence, Charles, 1942-1943 (Box 32, Folder 455)
          - Meaney, Thomas, 1942-1943 (Box 32, Folder 456)
          - Walker, Thomas, 1940 (Box 32, Folder 457)
        - Oaths of civilians, 1943 (Box 32, Folder 458)
        - Office of War Information, 1941-1943 (Box 32, Folder 459-460)
        - Office of War Information, 1942-1943 (Box 33, Folder 461-462)
        - Pearl Harbor trials, 1944 (Box 33, Folder 463)
        - Plant seizure and organization (Connally bill), 1938-1944 (Box 33, Folder 464-467)
        - Political statements, 1944 (Box 33, Folder 468)
        - Poll tax, 1941-1943 (Box 33, Folder 469)
        - Private suits arising out of frauds against the U.S, 1942-1943 (Box 33, Folder 470)
        - Private suits arising out of frauds against the U.S., 1942-1943 (Box 34, Folder 471-472)
        - War Security Act, 1942-1943 (Box 34, Folder 473)
      - Patents
        - Hartford-Empire Company vs. USA, 1943 (Box 34, Folder 474)
        - National defense, 1942-1943 (Box 34, Folder 475)
        - Trademarks, 1943-1944 (Box 34, Folder 476)
        - Miscellanea, 1942-1944 (Box 35, Folder 477-478)
      - Silver
        - Special committee, 1942-1943 (Box 35, Folder 479)
        - War use, 1942-1944 (Box 35, Folder 480)
  - Bills
    - Bartley-McCormack: H.R. 1776, 1941 (Box 36, Folder 481)
    - Brainerd, E. H.: S. 1233, 1939 (Box 36, Folder 482)
    - Economic stabilization: S.J.R. 161, 1942 (Box 36, Folder 483)
    - Egan, Mary; S. 1509, 1939 (Box 36, Folder 484)
    - Finland aid: S. 3069, 1940 (Box 36, Folder 485)
    - Finland and Russia: S.C.R. 35, 1940 (Box 36, Folder 486)
    - Greenback issue: S.J.R. 56, 1939 (Box 36, Folder 487)
    - Ickes stamp: S.R. 296, 1940 (Box 36, Folder 488-489)
    - Income tax, 1939-1942 (Box 36, Folder 490)
    - Lane, Jame H.: S. 2264, 1941 (Box 36, Folder 491)
    - Lend-Lease: H.R. 1776, 1941 (Box 36, Folder 492)
    - Marine Fisheries: S. 1972, H.J.R. 302, S.J.R. 139, 1939-1942 (Box 36, Folder 493-495)
    - Nationality Act: S.R. 967, H.R. 2207, 1940 (Box 37, Folder 496)
    - Neilson, Chris: S. 2832, 1939. (Box 37, Folder 497)
    - Owen, Roy: H.R. 5794, 1942 (Box 37, Folder 498)
    - Patents: S. 1308, H.R. 3130, 1943 (Box 37, Folder 499)
    - Postwar foreign policy: S.R. 192, 1943 (Box 37, Folder 500)
    - Rubey, George: S. 1723, 1939 (Box 37, Folder 501)
    - Salary lists, prohibition: S.1900, 1939 (Box 37, Folder 502-503)
    - Senator Russell's report: S.R. 191, 1943 (Box 37, Folder 504)
    - Servicemen's vote: S. 1285; S. 1612, 1943 (Box 37, Folder 505)
    - Timber products: S. 680, S.J. 50, 1939 (Box 37, Folder 506)
    - Transport of oil, gas: H.R. 6430, 1942 (Box 37, Folder 507-508)
    - Turney, Matthew: S. 4351, 1940 (Box 37, Folder 509)
    - Weigland, George: "Relief of Heirs", 1939 (Box 37, Folder 510)
    - West Virginia senator: S.R. 106, 1941 (Box 37, Folder 511)
  - Campaign 1938
    - General, 1938 September-November (Box 38, Folder 512-518)
    - Congratulations, 1938 November (Box 38, Folder 519-521)
    - Congratulations, 1938 November (Box 39, Folder 522-525)
    - Congratulations, 1938 December (Box 39, Folder 526-527)
- U.S. SENATE SUBJECT FILES, 1919-1953; Series II; 7.75 linear feet (19 boxes)
  This series is arranged in alphabetical order by topic.
  - Aid to Allies
    See also: box 53, folder 652
    - Committee to Defend America, 1940-1941 (Box 40, Folder 528-529)
    - Credits to Britain, undated (Box 40, Folder 530)
    - Destroyer transaction, 1940-1943 (Box 40, Folder 531)
    - Flying fortresses and bombers, 1940 (Box 40, Folder 532)
    - Munitions data, 1940-1941 (Box 40, Folder 533)
    - Stimson and Knox, 1940-1941 (Box 40, Folder 534)
    - "Union Now", 1940, 1942 (Box 40, Folder 535-556)
  - Aid to Britain, 1941 (Box 40, Folder 537)
  - Amendments, 1941 (Box 40, Folder 538)
  - America First Committee, 1941 (Box 40, Folder 539)
  - Appointment books, 1940-1941 (Box 41, Folder 540)
  - Arbitration, 1938 (Box 41, Folder 541)
  - Arming merchantmen, 1941 (Box 41, Folder 542)
  - Banking and Currency
    - Federal Reserve Bank, 1941 (Box 41, Folder 543)
    - Foreign funds control, 1941 (Box 41, Folder 544)
    - General, 1939 (Box 41, Folder 545)
    - Import-export, legislation, 1940 (Box 41, Folder 546)
    - Miscellanea, undated (Box 41, Folder 547)
    - National monetary and banking policy, 1940-1941 (Box 41, Folder 548)
    - Securities Exchange Commission, 1934-1943 (Box 41, Folder 549)
    - Spending-Lending bill, 1939 (Box 41, Folder 550)
    - Stabilization and devaluation, 1939 (Box 42, Folder 551)
    - Trust indentures, 1939 (Box 42, Folder 552-554)
  - Berle statement, undated (Box 42, Folder 555)
  - Biddle, Francis, 1942 (Box 42, Folder 556)
  - Bureaucracy, 1944 (Box 42, Folder 557)
  - Business and finance, 1938-1940 (Box 42, Folder 558)
  - Catholics and the war, 1941 (Box 43, Folder 559)
  - Catholic Church, 1939, 1944 (Box 43, Folder 560)
  - Churchill, Winston, 1938, 1941 (Box 43, Folder 561)
  - Congress, 1942-1943 (Box 43, Folder 562-563)
  - Connecticut
    - General, undated (Box 43, Folder 564)
      - Governmental, 1930-1942 (Box 43, Folder 565)
      - Health, 1941-1943 (Box 43, Folder 566)
      - Political, 1938-1944 (Box 43, Folder 567-569)
      - Republican State Convention, 1940 (Box 44, Folder 570)
      - Social Security, 1943-1944 (Box 44, Folder 571)
      - Waterbury trial, 1939 (Box 44, Folder 572a)
  - Conscription, 1941 (Box 44, Folder 572b-573)
  - Conspiracy Act, 1939 (Box 44, Folder 574)
  - Constitution, 1933-1943 (Box 44, Folder 575)
  - Copyrights, 1939-1940 (Box 44, Folder 576)
  - Corporations, 1940-1941 (Box 44, Folder 577)
  - Courts, 1940 (Box 44, Folder 578)
  - Export-Import Bank of Washington, 1940 (Box 45, Folder 579)
  - Fillmore, Millard, [ca. 1941] (Box 45, Folder 580)
  - Finland legislation, 1928-1940 (Box 45, Folder 581)
  - Future: peace and war, 1919-1944 (Box 45, Folder 582-583)
  - Gold, 1939-1943 (Box 45, Folder 584)
  - Humor in the Record, 1944 (Box 46, Folder 585)
  - Hurley, Robert, 1944 (Box 46, Folder 586)
  - Inflation, 1941 (Box 46, Folder 587)
  - Ireland, 1939-1944 (Box 46, Folder 588)
  - Jefferson, Thomas, 1936, 1939 (Box 46, Folder 589)
  - Jews, 1941-1942 (Box 46, Folder 590-591)
  - Johnson, Edward, 1944 (Box 46, Folder 592)
  - Judiciary, 1936-1943 (Box 46, Folder 593)
  - Kellogg-Briand Pact, 1941 (Box 46, Folder 594)
  - Labor, 1938-1942 (Box 47, Folder 595-601)
  - Land titles (Indian lands), 1938 (Box 47, Folder 602)
  - Lawyers, 1935 (Box 47, Folder 603)
  - Legislative process, 1940 (Box 47, Folder 604)
  - Lend-Lease
    - Background, 1928-1943 (Box 48, Folder 605-608)
    - Correspondence and notes, 1941, 1944 (Box 48, Folder 609)
    - Hearing, 1941 (Box 48, Folder 610)
    - Hearing, 1941 (Box 49, Folder 611-612)
    - H.R. 1776, 1941-1942 (Box 49, Folder 613)
  - Lending agencies, 1943 (Box 49, Folder 614)
  - Luce, Clare Booth, 1943-1944 (Box 49, Folder 615)
  - McMahon, Brien, 1944 (Box 49, Folder 616)
  - Mail, record of incoming, 1943 (Box 49, Folder 617)
  - Miller - Tydings amendment (Fair Trade Act), 1938-1939 (Box 49, Folder 618)
  - Money and monetary policy, 1941, 1944 (Box 49, Folder 619)
  - Money and monetary policy, 1935-1940 (Box 50, Folder 620)
  - Monopolies, 1938-1941 (Box 50, Folder 621-622)
  - Munich Peace Pact, 1938 (Box 50, Folder 623)
  - Neutrality
    - Background, 1939 (Box 50, Folder 624-628)
    - Legislation, 1935-1942 (Box 51, Folder 629-630)
    - Propaganda and data, 1939-1940 (Box 51, Folder 631)
    - Statements, 1939 (Box 51, Folder 632)
  - Notes from Roberts Report, 1941 (Box 51, Folder 633)
  - Office
    - Filing system, [ca. 1939-1943] (Box 51, Folder 634-637)
    - Account book, appointment book, 1939-1943 (Box 51, Folder 638)
      General
      See also; box 49, folder 617
  - Office of War Information, 1942, 1944 (Box 52, Folder 639)
  - Oil and gas, 1934, 1939, 1941 (Box 52, Folder 640)
  - Palestine, 1939-1944 (Box 52, Folder 641-642)
  - Patents, 1934, 1939-1941 (Box 52, Folder 643)
  - Patman chain stores, 1939, 1940 (Box 52, Folder 644)
  - Peace, 1939-1941 (Box 52, Folder 645)
  - Pearl Harbor, 1942, 1944 (Box 52, Folder 646)
  - Personal, laudatory, 1944, undated (Box 52, Folder 647)
  - Petition, May 1941 (Box 52, Folder 648)
  - Photographs, [ca. 1938-1953], n. d (Box 53, Folder 649)
  - Political
    See also: box 54, folder 671-72
    - General, 1940-1944 (Box 53, Folder 650-651)
    - Aid to Allies, 1934, 1940 (Box 53, Folder 652)
    - Alien registration, 1939-1941 (Box 53, Folder 653)
    - Ashurst, Henry, 1940 (Box 53, Folder 654a)
    - Baldwin, Raymond E., 1944 (Box 53, Folder 654b)
    - Bail bonds, 1939 (Box 53, Folder 655)
    - Campaigns, 1938, 1940 (Box 53, Folder 656-657)
    - Communism, 1945, 1946, undated (Box 53, Folder 658)
    - Connecticut, 1938 (Box 53, Folder 659-660)
    - Hatch Act, 1939-1940 (Box 53, Folder 661)
    - Postwar economics, 1942-1944 (Box 53, Folder 662)
    - Republican National Committee, 1940 (Box 54, Folder 663)
    - Republican Party, 1939, 1940 (Box 54, Folder 664)
    - Third term, 1940 (Box 54, Folder 665-666)
  - Presidential powers, 1938-1941 (Box 54, Folder 667)
  - Price controls, 1941 (Box 54, Folder 668)
  - Propaganda for war, 1939-1941 (Box 54, Folder 669-670)
  - Republican Program Committee, 1938 (Box 54, Folder 671)
  - Republican sponsored legislation, 1933-1941 (Box 54, Folder 672)
  - Roosevelt, Franklin D., 1938-1944 (Box 54, Folder 673)
  - Saint Lawrence Waterway, 1925, 1927, 1932-1933, 1940-1941, 1944 (Box 55, Folder 674)
  - Silver/Gold, 1934, 1939, 1941-1942 (Box 55, Folder 675-676)
  - Speeches, 1939-1941 (Box 55, Folder 677-686)
  - Speeches, 1940-1944 (Box 56, Folder 687-690)
  - Spy system, 1939, undated (Box 56, Folder 691)
  - Swift, Zephaniah, 1940 (Box 56, Folder 692)
  - Treaties, 1923-1944 (Box 56, Folder 693-694)
  - U.S. foreign policy
    - Background, 1940-1941 (Box 56, Folder 695-696)
    - Neutrality, 1939-1941 (Box 56, Folder 697-698)
    - Campaign, 1944 (Box 56, Folder 699)
  - Voting records, 1939-1944 (Box 57, Folder 700-705)
  - War in Europe, 1940-1941 (Box 58, Folder 706)
  - Webster, Daniel, undated (Box 58, Folder 707)
  - White, William A., 1940 (Box 58, Folder 708)
  - Wilkie, Wendell, 1941-1944 (Box 58, Folder 709)
  - World War II, 1932-1941 (Box 58, Folder 710-711)
  - Miscellanea, 1938-1939, 1943-1944, undated (Box 58, Folder 712a)
- GENERAL FILES, 1916-1979; Series III; 6 linear feet (16 boxes)
  This series is arranged in five sections: General, Select, Chronological, Speeches, Scrapbooks.
  - General
    - A, 1945-1953 (Box 59, Folder 712b)
    - B, 1945-1953 (Box 59, Folder 713-714)
    - C, 1945-1953 (Box 59, Folder 715-716)
    - D, 1945-1953 (Box 59, Folder 717-718)
    - E, 1945-1953 (Box 59, Folder 719)
    - F, 1945-1953 (Box 59, Folder 720)
    - G, 1945-1953 (Box 60, Folder 721-722)
    - H, 1945-1953 (Box 60, Folder 723-724)
    - I - K, 1945-1953 (Box 60, Folder 725)
    - L, 1945-1953 (Box 60, Folder 726)
    - M, 1945-1953 (Box 60, Folder 727-728)
    - N - P, 1945-1953 (Box 60, Folder 729)
    - R, 1945-1953 (Box 61, Folder 730-731)
    - S, 1945-1953 (Box 61, Folder 732-733)
    - T, 1945-1953 (Box 61, Folder 734)
    - W - Z, 1945-1953 (Box 61, Folder 735)
  - Select
    - Amarillo trip, 1947-1948 (Box 61, Folder 736)
    - Baldwin, Raymond E., 1947-1949 (Box 61, Folder 737)
    - Banquets, 1947 (Box 61, Folder 738)
    - Bar association, 1948-1951 (Box 61, Folder 739)
    - Borchard, Edwin, 1945, 1952 (Box 61, Folder 740)
    - Campaigns
      - Congratulations, 1932 (Box 61, Folder 741)
      - Senate elections, 1946 (Box 61, Folder 742)
      - 1948, 1946-1949 (Box 62, Folder 743-744)
      - 1952, 1951-1952 (Box 62, Folder 745-746)
      - Political correspondence: Connecticut, 1933-1936 (Box 62, Folder 747-749)
      - Political correspondence: Connecticut, 1948-1953 (Box 62, Folder 754-751)
    - Copper tax suspension, 1947-1951 (Box 63, Folder 752)
    - Cross, Wilbur, 1935-1937 (Box 63, Folder 753)
    - Danaher, Fahy, and Poole, 1947, 1949, 1970 (Box 63, Folder 754)
    - Defense contract articles, 1949 (Box 63, Folder 755)
    - Fay, Charles Jarvis, 1940-1946 (Box 63, Folder 756)
    - Foreign policy, 1944 (Box 63, Folder 757)
    - Gridiron Club, 1946-1953, 1964-1969 (Box 63, Folder 758-759)
    - Horty, Thomas E., 1949 (Box 63, Folder 760)
    - Idaho trip, 1965 (Box 63, Folder 761)
    - Invitations, 1954-1957 (Box 63, Folder 762-765)
    - Invitations, 1958-1966 (Box 64, Folder 766-770)
    - Legal: Brown v. Smith, 1931-1951 (Box 64, Folder 771)
    - Legislation: Senate committee, 1951 (Box 64, Folder 772)
    - Letters of congratulation, 1945, 1947 (Box 64, Folder 773)
    - Link, Henry C., 1947-1951 (Box 64, Folder 774)
    - National Religion and Labor Foundation, 1931-1946 (Box 64, Folder 775)
    - Nixon, Richard, 1946-1951, 1971 (Box 64, Folder 776)
    - Personal, 1947-1968 (Box 65, Folder 777-785)
    - Personal expenses, 1955-1965 (Box 65, Folder 786)
    - Pettee, Edith, 1945 (Box 66, Folder 787)
    - Political, 1940-1942, 1945-1948 (Box 66, Folder 788-790)
    - President's Commission on Internal Security and Individual Rights, 1950-1951 (Box 66, Folder 791-794)
    - Reciprocal trade data, 1943 (Box 66, Folder 795)
    - Republican National Committee, 1952-1953 (Box 67, Folder 796-799)
    - Republican Party congressional aide, 1944-1946, 1952 (Box 67, Folder 800-802)
    - Republican State Central Committee, 1945-1952 (Box 67, Folder 803)
    - Senators, 1945-1953 (Box 68, Folder 804-807)
    - U.S. Attorney General, 1922-1926 (Box 68, Folder 808)
    - U.S. District Judge, 1930-1931 (Box 68, Folder 809)
    - Walcott, Frederic, 1948, 1971 (Box 68, Folder 810)
    - Western trip, 1946 (Box 68, Folder 811)
    - Wheaton, Raymond, 1937 (Box 68, Folder 812)
    - William H. Taft, III dinner, 1952-1953 (Box 68, Folder 813)
  - Chronological
    - 1921-1936 (Box 69, Folder 814)
    - 1938-1947 (Box 69, Folder 815-816)
    - 1950-1952 (Box 69, Folder 817)
    - 1955-1959 (Box 69, Folder 818)
    - 1965-1970 (Box 69, Folder 819-820)
    - 1923-1979 (Box 69, Folder 821)
  - Speeches
    - 1928-1933 (Box 70, Folder 822-823)
    - 1935 (Box 70, Folder 824)
    - 1938 (Box 70, Folder 825-826)
    - 1940-1941 (Box 70, Folder 827-828)
    - 1943-1944 (Box 70, Folder 829-833)
    - 1944-1951 (Box 71, Folder 834-837)
    - Drafts, undated (Box 71, Folder 838-840)
    - Background material, 1949-1951 (Box 71, Folder 841)
    - Senators', 1945-1947 (Box 71, Folder 842)
  - Scrapbooks
    - 1916, 1933-1945, 1952 (Box 72, Folder 842)